citizenwatch.com 2017-12-09

# PRIVACY AND COOKIES POLICY - Citizen Watch - English (UK)

Citizen Watch United Kingdom Limited. (“CUK”, “we”, or “us”) is committed to respecting your online privacy and to the appropriate protection and handling of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you provide to us.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify you and includes, for example, first and/or last name, postal address, email address, telephone number, or other contact information.

The following statement sets out how we will use information that you provide to us via the website: www.citizenwatch.com (the ‘Site’) and/or other social media such as Facebook and Twitter.

## What information do we collect?

In general, you may visit the pages on this Site without revealing any Personal Information about yourself. However, we may collect Personal Information from you when you: purchase products from us, register a purchased product with us; participate in on-line surveys; wish to make certain on-line information requests from us; and/or participate in on-line contests, sweepstakes, promotions and discussions sponsored by us on this Site and/or via social media such as Facebook and Twitter.

The type of information so requested or collected by us may include user contact information (like your name, mailing address, and email address), billing Information (like credit card number and expiration date) and user demographic information (like your post code, age or income level).

## How will we use your information?

We will use your information in the following ways:  
• to ensure that our Site’s content is presented as effectively as possible for you;  
• for our internal purposes, such as quality control, Site performance, system administration and to evaluate use of our Site so that we can provide enhanced services;  
• to notify you about changes to our services;  
• to provide you with information products or services that you request from us, or which we feel may be of interest to you (provided of course that you agree);  
• to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts with you and for billing and delivery purposes; and  
• to enable you to participate in interactive features on the Site when you choose to do so.

If you choose to provide Personal Information, we may use it ourselves or share it with our affiliates who provide services to us. We do not otherwise share, sell, or lease Personal Information to any third parties for their marketing or other uses. We may disclose Personal Information to governmental authorities when legally required to do so, and may cooperate with such authorities investigating claims of illegal activities including, but not limited to, illegal transfer of copyrighted material, fraud, and/or postings or e-mail messages containing threats of violence.

## Children’s Privacy

This Site is not structured, nor intended, to attract children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly solicit or collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## Collected Information

Some of the pages on this Site may use “cookies” and other tracking technologies.

A “cookie” is a small data file placed and stored on your computer’s hard drive which allows our servers to identify the computer accessing our Site in order to track statistical information about navigation through the Site and whether that computer has previously visited our Site. The cookie is not used to obtain Personal Information and the information is tracked only to improve Site navigation, to monitor activity on the Site, to diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our Site and to identify content preferences. We may also use Personal Information in connection with cookie data to provide you with additional information regarding content you have viewed and/or to suggest other of our products, services, and/or information which we believe may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to accept cookies, most browsers can be set to block them or to alert you before one is placed. It is your responsibility to set the appropriate parameters on your browser. However, please be aware that if you reject or disable cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all the features or services available on the Site.

We may also use “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, and clear GIF’s). Web beacons are used for internal purposes, such as to obtain the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page(s) on which the web beacon appears, the URL of the page(s) on which the web beacon appears, the time the page(s) containing the web beacon was viewed, and the type of browser used to view the page(s). We also retain service providers who use web beacons to assess the effectiveness of our e-mail and other communications and for us to learn what pages our visitors viewed and what appeals to them.

## The cookies we us on the site are:

• The Cookie Citizen_userLocaleSelect is used to identify and store your geographical location in order to display the correct website for the country in which you reside.

## Links to, and Interactions with, Other Sites

This Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the security, privacy practices, or the content of such web sites. Those websites may have different privacy practices, policies, and procedures and we encourage you to read them.

We maintain a mobile version of this Site and this Privacy Policy applies to that version as well.

We maintain a presence on social media including Facebook  and Twitter. We may collect information you post on social media, including but not limited to your postings on our social media pages and/or feeds, and use it in connection with the Personal Information we obtain on this Site in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Marketing

We may use your information to provide you with marketing information that you request or that we feel may interest you by post and/or telephone.

If you are an existing customer, we may contact you by email and/or telephone with information about products and services which are similar to those we previously provided to you, unless you have indicated that you do not want to hear from us.

If you are a new customer, we may contact you by email and/or telephone, only if you consent.

If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please tick the relevant boxes on the form when we collect your information. You may ask us at any time not to use your information for marketing purposes by contacting us at marketing@citizenwatch.co.uk.

You will also notice that in all free email subscriptions generated by us there is an unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message. Simply click on this link to go to a page that allows you to unsubscribe from any or all of the lists you are subscribed to. Citizen Watch United Kingdom Limited DOES NOT participate in mass or unsolicited email practices (commonly referred to as SPAM).

## Where do we transfer your information to?

We will not transfer your information to, or store it, outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”).

##  User-Generated Content

In conjunction with our affiliate Olapic we also capture Citizen branded user-generated content, for example an image of a Citizen Watch shared on Instagram, for use in digital and offline media. We ask for permission from the original content creator before any of this content is utilised and all user information is held on our behalf by Olapic and used in a manner in-keeping with our Privacy Policy. For full terms and conditions of the Olapic platform, please visit this page: http://www.olapic.com/privacy-policy/

## Customer Reviews

In conjunction with our affiliate Bazaar Voice we will also capture Citizen customer reviews for use in digital and offline media. These reviews may also be utilised for use on our Retail Partner’s websites. In keeping with our Privacy Policy, all private customer information is held by Bazaar Voice and is shared with Citizen and our Retail Partners securely. Only the information relevant to the review is displayed on either Citizen’s or Retail Partner’s Sites.

## How do we keep your information secure? 

All your information is stored on secure servers. Information stored from our watch registration programme is held on secure servers on our behalf by our marketing partner Customer Minds Ltd.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will apply our normal procedures and comply with legal requirements to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Site and any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Your rights

This Site gives users the option to request changes, modifications, or deletions to or from Personal Information previously provided. Please email your request to: marketing@citizenwatch.co.uk

You have the right to access your information and should direct any request for your information to us at marketing@citizenwatch.co.uk. Please note that a fee of ten pounds (£10.00) may be payable to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Changes to This Policy

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. We will post changes to this policy here, so be sure to check back periodically. We may also decide to notify our users by e-mail of significant changes.

## Your Consent

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to CUK’s collection and use of the Personal Information and other information for the purposes described above.

## How to contact us

Questions, comments or requests concerning this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to us at marketing@citizenwatch.co.uk.
